var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "إِذِ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "rootWordId": 26,
        "tlit": "idhi",
        "frequency": 239,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " إِذِ انْبَعَثَ أَشْقَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "إِذ",
        "rootWordType": "time adverb",
        "wazn": "إِذ",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idh",
        "waznType": "Time adverb",
        "waznFreq": 239,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": 409,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْقَمَرِ إِذَا تَلَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 409,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": 409,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالنَّهَارِ إِذَا جَلَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 409,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": 409,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّيْلِ إِذَا يَغْشَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 409,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "And the earth",
        "pcklId": "458",
        "rootWordId": 32,
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": 461,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْأَرْضِ وَمَا طَحَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "أ ر ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ر ض",
        "waznEnglish": "the Earth, land",
        "waznTlit": "hamza rā ḍād",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 461,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2834",
        "rootWordId": 61,
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": 2851,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَقَالَ لَهُمْ رَسُولُ اللَّهِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱللَّه",
        "waznEnglish": "Allah",
        "waznTlit": "allah",
        "waznType": "Proper noun",
        "waznFreq": 2699,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2835",
        "rootWordId": 61,
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": 2851,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " نَاقَةَ اللَّهِ وَسُقْيَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱللَّه",
        "waznEnglish": "Allah",
        "waznTlit": "allah",
        "waznType": "Proper noun",
        "waznFreq": 2699,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "انْبَعَثَ",
        "answer": "(was) sent forth",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "rootWordId": 137,
        "tlit": "inbaʿatha",
        "frequency": 67,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " إِذِ انْبَعَثَ أَشْقَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ب ع ث",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱنۢبَعَثَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to send forth",
        "waznTlit": "inbaʿatha",
        "waznType": "Verb (form VII)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنَاهَا",
        "answer": "constructed it",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 160,
        "tlit": "banāhā",
        "frequency": 184,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالسَّمَاءِ وَمَا بَنَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ب ن ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بَنَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to construct, to build",
        "waznTlit": "banā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 11,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَلَاهَا",
        "answer": "it follows it",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "rootWordId": 188,
        "tlit": "talāhā",
        "frequency": 63,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْقَمَرِ إِذَا تَلَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ت ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَلَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to recite",
        "waznTlit": "talā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 61,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "جَلَّاهَا",
        "answer": "it displays it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 257,
        "tlit": "jallāhā",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالنَّهَارِ إِذَا جَلَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ج ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَلَّىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to reveal",
        "waznTlit": "jallā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخَافُ",
        "answer": "He fears",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "rootWordId": 444,
        "tlit": "yakhāfu",
        "frequency": 124,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 15,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا يَخَافُ عُقْبَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "خ و ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَافَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to fear, to be afraid",
        "waznTlit": "khāfa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 83,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "خَابَ",
        "answer": "he fails",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 448,
        "tlit": "khāba",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَقَدْ خَابَ مَنْ دَسَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "خ ي ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَابَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to fail",
        "waznTlit": "khāba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "دَسَّاهَا",
        "answer": "buries it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 472,
        "tlit": "dassāhā",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَقَدْ خَابَ مَنْ دَسَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "د س و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "د س و",
        "waznEnglish": "to bury",
        "waznTlit": "dāl sīn wāw",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَدَمْدَمَ",
        "answer": "So destroyed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 482,
        "tlit": "fadamdama",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَكَذَّبُوهُ فَعَقَرُوهَا فَدَمْدَمَ عَلَيْهِمْ رَبُّهُمْ بِذَنْبِهِمْ فَسَوَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "د م د م",
        "rootWordType": "quadriliteral root",
        "wazn": "د م د م",
        "waznEnglish": "to destroy",
        "waznTlit": "dāl mīm dāl mīm",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذَنْبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for their sin",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "rootWordId": 515,
        "tlit": "bidhanbihim",
        "frequency": 39,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " فَكَذَّبُوهُ فَعَقَرُوهَا فَدَمْدَمَ عَلَيْهِمْ رَبُّهُمْ بِذَنْبِهِمْ فَسَوَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ذ ن ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذَنب",
        "waznEnglish": "for their sins",
        "waznTlit": "dhanb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 37,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "954",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbuhum",
        "frequency": 980,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " فَكَذَّبُوهُ فَعَقَرُوهَا فَدَمْدَمَ عَلَيْهِمْ رَبُّهُمْ بِذَنْبِهِمْ فَسَوَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 975,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولُ",
        "answer": "(the) Messenger",
        "pcklId": "470",
        "rootWordId": 555,
        "tlit": "rasūlu",
        "frequency": 513,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَقَالَ لَهُمْ رَسُولُ اللَّهِ نَاقَةَ اللَّهِ وَسُقْيَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ر س ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَسُول",
        "waznEnglish": "[We] have sent you",
        "waznTlit": "rasūl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 332,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "زَكَّاهَا",
        "answer": "purifies it",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "rootWordId": 624,
        "tlit": "zakkāhā",
        "frequency": 59,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 9,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " قَدْ أَفْلَحَ مَنْ زَكَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ز ك و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "زَكَّىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to purify",
        "waznTlit": "zakkā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 12,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسُقْيَاهَا",
        "answer": "and her drink",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "rootWordId": 704,
        "tlit": "wasuq'yāhā",
        "frequency": 25,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " فَقَالَ لَهُمْ رَسُولُ اللَّهِ نَاقَةَ اللَّهِ وَسُقْيَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "س ق ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سُقْيَٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "water",
        "waznTlit": "suq'yā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "And the heaven",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "rootWordId": 726,
        "tlit": "wal-samāi",
        "frequency": 381,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالسَّمَاءِ وَمَا بَنَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "س م و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَمَآء",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] (have) named her",
        "waznTlit": "samā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 310,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَّاهَا",
        "answer": "proportioned it",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "rootWordId": 747,
        "tlit": "sawwāhā",
        "frequency": 83,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَنَفْسٍ وَمَا سَوَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "س و ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَوَّىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to fashion, to proportion",
        "waznTlit": "sawwā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 13,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَوَّاهَا",
        "answer": "and leveled them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "rootWordId": 747,
        "tlit": "fasawwāhā",
        "frequency": 83,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " فَكَذَّبُوهُ فَعَقَرُوهَا فَدَمْدَمَ عَلَيْهِمْ رَبُّهُمْ بِذَنْبِهِمْ فَسَوَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "س و ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَوَّىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to fashion, to proportion",
        "waznTlit": "sawwā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 13,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْقَاهَا",
        "answer": "(the) most wicked of them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "rootWordId": 788,
        "tlit": "ashqāhā",
        "frequency": 12,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " إِذِ انْبَعَثَ أَشْقَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ش ق و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَشْقَى",
        "waznEnglish": "were wretched",
        "waznTlit": "ashqā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّمْسِ",
        "answer": "By the sun",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "rootWordId": 797,
        "tlit": "wal-shamsi",
        "frequency": 33,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالشَّمْسِ وَضُحَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ش م س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ش م س",
        "waznEnglish": "the sun",
        "waznTlit": "shīn mīm sīn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 33,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضُحَاهَا",
        "answer": "and its brightness",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 882,
        "tlit": "waḍuḥāhā",
        "frequency": 7,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالشَّمْسِ وَضُحَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ض ح و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ضُحًى",
        "waznEnglish": "exposed to the sun's heat",
        "waznTlit": "ḍuḥan",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 6,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "طَحَاهَا",
        "answer": "spread it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 905,
        "tlit": "ṭaḥāhā",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْأَرْضِ وَمَا طَحَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ط ح و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ط ح و",
        "waznEnglish": "to spread",
        "waznTlit": "ṭā ḥā wāw",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِطَغْوَاهَا",
        "answer": "by their transgression",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "rootWordId": 913,
        "tlit": "biṭaghwāhā",
        "frequency": 39,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 11,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " كَذَّبَتْ ثَمُودُ بِطَغْوَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ط غ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَغْوَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "transgress",
        "waznTlit": "ṭaghwā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عُقْبَاهَا",
        "answer": "its consequences",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "rootWordId": 1009,
        "tlit": "ʿuq'bāhā",
        "frequency": 80,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 15,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا يَخَافُ عُقْبَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ع ق ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عُقْبَى",
        "waznEnglish": "look back",
        "waznTlit": "ʿuq'bā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 6,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَقَرُوهَا",
        "answer": "and they hamstrung her",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 1011,
        "tlit": "faʿaqarūhā",
        "frequency": 8,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَكَذَّبُوهُ فَعَقَرُوهَا فَدَمْدَمَ عَلَيْهِمْ رَبُّهُمْ بِذَنْبِهِمْ فَسَوَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ع ق ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَقَرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to hamstrung",
        "waznTlit": "ʿaqara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 5,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْشَاهَا",
        "answer": "it covers it",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "rootWordId": 1064,
        "tlit": "yaghshāhā",
        "frequency": 29,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّيْلِ إِذَا يَغْشَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "غ ش و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "غَشِيَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to cover",
        "waznTlit": "ghashiya",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 13,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فُجُورَهَا",
        "answer": "(to distinguish) its wickedness",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "rootWordId": 1108,
        "tlit": "fujūrahā",
        "frequency": 24,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَلْهَمَهَا فُجُورَهَا وَتَقْوَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ف ج ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "فُجُور",
        "waznEnglish": "you cause to gush forth",
        "waznTlit": "fujūr",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفْلَحَ",
        "answer": "he succeeds",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "rootWordId": 1151,
        "tlit": "aflaḥa",
        "frequency": 40,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 9,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " قَدْ أَفْلَحَ مَنْ زَكَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ف ل ح",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَفْلَحَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to succeed",
        "waznTlit": "aflaḥa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 27,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرِ",
        "answer": "And the moon",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "rootWordId": 1229,
        "tlit": "wal-qamari",
        "frequency": 27,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْقَمَرِ إِذَا تَلَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ق م ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ق م ر",
        "waznEnglish": "the moon",
        "waznTlit": "qāf mīm rā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 27,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "But said",
        "pcklId": "1612",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَقَالَ لَهُمْ رَسُولُ اللَّهِ نَاقَةَ اللَّهِ وَسُقْيَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَالَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to say",
        "waznTlit": "qāla",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1618,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَتْ",
        "answer": "Denied",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "rootWordId": 1263,
        "tlit": "kadhabat",
        "frequency": 282,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 11,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " كَذَّبَتْ ثَمُودُ بِطَغْوَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ك ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَذَّبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to deny, to reject",
        "waznTlit": "kadhaba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 176,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبُوهُ",
        "answer": "But they denied him",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "rootWordId": 1263,
        "tlit": "fakadhabūhu",
        "frequency": 282,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَكَذَّبُوهُ فَعَقَرُوهَا فَدَمْدَمَ عَلَيْهِمْ رَبُّهُمْ بِذَنْبِهِمْ فَسَوَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ك ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَذَّبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to deny, to reject",
        "waznTlit": "kadhaba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 176,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَلْهَمَهَا",
        "answer": "And He inspired it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1354,
        "tlit": "fa-alhamahā",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَلْهَمَهَا فُجُورَهَا وَتَقْوَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ل ه م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ل ه م",
        "waznEnglish": "to inspire",
        "waznTlit": "lām hā mīm",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "And the night",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "rootWordId": 1364,
        "tlit": "wa-al-layli",
        "frequency": 92,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّيْلِ إِذَا يَغْشَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ل ي ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "لَيْل",
        "waznEnglish": "of the night",
        "waznTlit": "layl",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 84,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "And (the) soul",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "rootWordId": 1500,
        "tlit": "wanafsin",
        "frequency": 298,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَنَفْسٍ وَمَا سَوَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ن ف س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَفْس",
        "waznEnglish": "self, soul, person, mind",
        "waznTlit": "nafs",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 295,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "And the day",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "rootWordId": 1525,
        "tlit": "wal-nahāri",
        "frequency": 113,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالنَّهَارِ إِذَا جَلَّاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ن ه ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَهَار",
        "waznEnglish": "repel them",
        "waznTlit": "nahār",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 57,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاقَةَ",
        "answer": "(It is the) she-camel",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "rootWordId": 1533,
        "tlit": "nāqata",
        "frequency": 7,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " فَقَالَ لَهُمْ رَسُولُ اللَّهِ نَاقَةَ اللَّهِ وَسُقْيَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "ن و ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ن و ق",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) a she-camel",
        "waznTlit": "nūn wāw qāf",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 7,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَقْوَاهَا",
        "answer": "and its righteousness",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "rootWordId": 1641,
        "tlit": "wataqwāhā",
        "frequency": 258,
        "surahnum": 91,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَلْهَمَهَا فُجُورَهَا وَتَقْوَاهَا",
        "rootWord": "و ق ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَقْوَى",
        "waznEnglish": "and save us",
        "waznTlit": "taqwā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 17,
        "hasRootWord": true
    }
]; 
export default words;